- 嗨\n- 嘿 伙计们 最近怎么样?
Hey.Guys******
我来帮你喝光
******
我们刚与Stella的妹妹跟她的未婚夫吃饭\n他们要比我们先一步结婚
We******
你们知道一个女人从小的时候就\n幻想着一个完美的婚礼吗?
******
- 知道\n- 完全理解
- Yeah.\n- Totally
我妹妹完全把我的梦幻婚礼抢走了\n每一个细节
My******detail
地点在Shelter岛\n时间在黄昏
******
就在沙滩上的旧屋里\n跟我的家人一起度过
是我梦寐以求的婚礼
It's******
我来喝
******
这里的羊肉挺不错的
哦 我是个素食者 我一直认为\n吃荤其实是一种谋杀行为
******
当然我可能没有你们那么健壮
But******
那是因为你缺乏蛋白质
******
我要点羊肉
好的 新目标 我要我们的婚礼\n彻底把他们的比下去
Ok,******ass
我要把他们的婚礼扔进马桶\n然后冲够20次水
******
哦 Ted 在高中的时候 \n你恨死婚礼了 对吧？
Ted******
要知道 她总是想要把我比下去\n我爱她 但是在心里阴暗的一面还是希望她结不成婚
You******
我恨他 我恨他 我恨死他\n天 这牛排真好吃
I******good.
4天前 他去营养师那边\n咨询各种食物的维生素含量
******
我为他放弃了化妆品 放弃了淋浴\n放弃了剃腋毛
I******
真难以想象到底哪里出了问题
******
现在马上举行婚礼了 我真的很想要培根做餐点\n我很喜欢 但是不能修改了 得花上好几千美元
孩子们 当你们恋爱的时候\n两个人是有默契和感应的
Kids******
你说呢? 我们可以帮帮她
What do you think?\nWe could help her out.
不 Stella 我们应该帮帮她
No,Stella,weshould help her out.
我们出钱吧
Let's pay for dinner.
Nora 别担心
Nora. Don't worry.
我们来搞定
We got this.
没错
That's right.
我们会承包下你的婚礼\n把你花费的钱都还给你
We'll take over your wedding, pay\nyou back for everything you spent.
Ted和我这周日就结婚
Ted and I will get married this Sunday.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第5集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode05
我们周日结婚?
We're getting married this Sunday?
我们已经做好准备了吗?
Are we sure we're ready for this?
Ted 我浪费了几年的时间去\n说服Lucy的爸爸认为他已经准备好
Ted,I wasted years trying to get Lucy's\ndad to decide he was "ready" for this,
但他从来都没有准备好\n所以我们就永远结不了
but he never got ready for this.\nThat's why we never got married.
来吧 我们要主动出击
Come on,let's just be spontaneous.
我曾梦见过Tony也会那么主动
I used to dream that Tony\nwould be spontaneous like this.
好吧 我加入
Okay,I'm in.
我也...非常主动
And I'm also... spontaneous.
我真不该这么做
I wish I hadn't done that.
孩子们 通常故事的最后才会说出\n它的意义所在 不过这次是特别的重要
Kids,morals usually come at the end of\nstories, but this one is so important,
我要现在就告诉你们: \n永远不要邀请旧情人参加你的婚礼
I'm gonna tell you now: Don't\never,ever invite an ex to your wedding.
如果之前就有人告诫过我\n可能一切都将会不同
If someone had given me that advice,\nwell,it would have changed everything.
拜托 你一定得来 这是我的婚礼啊
Come on,you've got to\ncome, it's my wedding.
不行啊 我在东京
I can't. I'm in Tokyo.
这是我工作的第一个星期\n我不能就这样离开
It's my first week on the\njob. I can't just take off.
而且 我终于可以播报一些重要的新闻了
Plus,I'm finally doing serious news.
Robin的确是在播报重要的新闻
Robin was doing serious news.
那里是日本第一家英文新闻广播台
It was the number one\nEnglish news network in Japan.
不过 播报的方式有点不一样
Of course,the news was a\nlittle different over there.
巨型风扇!
******
美国联邦储备委员会投票决定...
The Federal Reserve Board\nvoted to leave interest...
维持利率不变
rates unchanged.
那是我的婚礼啊 你一定要到
It's my wedding. You have to be there.
好吧 好吧 我会参加的
Okay. Okay. I'll be there.
噢 我得挂了
Whoops,I gotta go.
晚上好
Good evening.
我是Robin Scherbatsky
And I'm Robin Scherbatsky.
中东的和平谈判再次陷入僵局
Peace talks were stalled\nonce again in the Middle East.
尽管谈判的开始是充满希望的\n可是就安全问题方面谈判破裂
Despite a promising start in the latest\nnegotiations, talks foundered on security issues.
- 她会来\n- 太好了!
- She's in.\n- Yes!
好了 Ted 今晚是你的单身派对
All right,Ted, your\nbachelor party,tonight.
我请了三个你见过的身体跟精神上\n都最棒的异国舞者...
I have got three of the most physically and\nmorally flexible exotic dancers you've ever seen...
不行 没时间了
Can't,there's no time.
好吧 我会告诉你以后的事情的
Okay, I'll let you know how it goes.
Marshall 我们得为明天租车 是吧?
Marshall,we should really\nrent the cars for tomorrow,huh?
没错
Sure.
什么?
What?
不 "不要结婚啊 Ted"?
No "Don't get married,Ted"?
不 "你这样做大错特错 Ted"?
No "You're making a big mistake,Ted"?
Barney Stinson...\nBarney Stinson...
你不再在婚姻问题上做反抗了吗?
are you no longer committed\nto the war on marriage?
不是 我只知道当我看到它的时候\n就知道已经毫无希望了
No,I just know a hopeless\ncause when I see it.
就跟我不会废物利用的道理一样
It's the same reason I don't recycle.
再说 Ted要结婚是我最为关注的事情
Plus,Ted getting married\nis in my best interest.
要知道...
You see...
最近我在致力于研究一个极为重要的问题
lately I've been working on a\nproblem of the utmost importance.
我不得不承认我一筹莫展
I confess I was stumped.
直到一个晚上我决定要把它彻底解决掉
Until one night I decided to\ntackle it once and for all.
我怎样才能再次跟ROBIN上床?
HOW CAN I HAVE SEX WITH ROBIN AGAIN?
心灵脆弱
VULNERABLE
念旧之情
NOSTALGIC
醉酒
BOOZE
最后 我破解了译码
Then,at last, I cracked the code.
在TED的婚礼上灌醉她
GET HER DRUNK AT TED'S WEDDING
这么说你又重新盯上了Robin
So you're back on Robin.
如果一切顺利的话
Hopefully.
这周末是跟她重修旧好的最好时机
I mean,this weekend is the best\nchance ever to hook up with her again.
会出现许多障碍的\n有太多的干扰了
You'll never pull it off.\nThere's too many distractions.
你要是见到第一个喝醉的伴娘
The first drunk bridesmaid you see,
你会像个旧时的摄影师\n把头钻进她的裙底里去的
you'll have your head under her\ndress like an old-time photographer.
Lily 别说得那么下流
Lily,don't cheapen this.
我不想听起来觉得既淫荡又浪漫
I don't want to sound all\nmushy-gushy and romantic,
但这个周末 Robin将会是我唯一会上的女人
but this weekend,Robin is\nthe only woman I'm banging.
于是 在婚礼的前一天 \nStella和我开车去Shelter岛
And so,the day before our wedding, Stella\nand I made the trip up to Shelter Island.
其他人也很快就到了
With everyone else not far behind.
Zitch dog
（找狗游戏术语 第二季Ted和Marshall玩过）
Zitch dog.
这里并非是我想象当中\nTed要结婚的地方
This isn't exactly where I\npictured Ted getting married.
"合十瑜伽班与坐禅兴趣团"
"The Namaste Yoga and\nMeditation Collective."
你们的想法我不清楚\n但是我想尽早离开这里
I don't know about you guys, but\nNama-stay here any longer than I have to.
亲爱的 去那个嬉皮女去打个招呼\n我们去拿些饮料
Sweetie,go check in with that dirty hippie\nover there and we'll get some drinks.
你们这里有什么样的威士忌?
So,what scotches you got?
哦 这个中心是严禁喝酒的
Oh,here at the center, we have\na very strict no-alcohol policy.
太好了 每顿饭全包了 对吧?
Great,and all the meals\nare included,right?
对 而且100%是素菜
Yep,and they're all 100% vegan.
不 我要喝酒
No. I need alcohol.
我怎么靠这个撂倒Robin呢
I'm not gonna get Robin with this stuff.
看这个 果浆搅拌大脑革命汁
Look at this. Berry\nBlaster Brain Revitalizer.
天啊 这些饮料还可能会让人变得聪明
My God,some of these drinks could\nactually make a girl smarter.
究竟Ted把我们带到什么鬼地方来?
What sort of hell has Ted brought us to?
- 没肉吃\n- 没酒喝
- There's no meat.\n- There's no alcohol.
还有更糟的呢: 我肯定刚才跟你们\n说话的人九成以前是Spin Doctors的主唱
It gets worse: I'm 90% sure that guy you were talking\nwith used to be lead singer of the Spin Doctors.
嘿 伙计们 Stella和我有些小麻烦
Hey,guys, Stella and I\nhave a little problem.
哦 这些节目都挺棒的
Oh,the programs look great.
只是上面写的不是我们的名字\n不然的话真的挺好的
I mean,it's not our names on the\nfront, but otherwise,really nice.
哦 嘿 我刚跟Robin通了电话
Oh,hey,I talked to Robin.
她可能会晚一些到\n不过她会来得及的
She's running a little bit late, but\nshe'll be here just under the wire.
你邀请了Robin?
You invited Robin?
对 没错
Yeah,of course.
你之前都没告诉我
You never told me that.
我不肯定我会乐意
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
允许我帮你一下?
Can I help?
你感到愉快
You feel glad.
你也喜欢Robin啊
You like Robin.
没错 只是她是你的前女友
Yeah,but she's your ex-girlfriend.
- 这样会怪怪的\n- 不会的
- It's weird.\n- It's not weird.
会的
It is weird.
你不会明白一个新娘在婚礼上\n看到新郎前女友的感觉
You don't get what it's like for a bride\nto see her groom's ex at their wedding.
喔 Stella
Oh,Stella.
你丈夫以前一天会上我三次
Your new husband used to nail\nme,like, three times a day.
把旧情人请过来 我不知道 会带来...
Having exes around, I\ndon't know, it brings up...
一些未知的麻烦
unresolved things.
你就能肯定你跟旧情人\n坐在一起不会旧情复炽?
How do you know that spark won't come\nback with your ex sitting out there?
得了吧 我们只是朋友
Come on, we're just friends.
在说 Robin跟我早就已经复炽过了...\n就上年的感恩节 也没多久的事
Plus,Robin and I already had our backslide--\nlast Thanksgiving, not even that long ago.
你这不是自相矛盾吗?
Did you place a large bet\nagainst yourself in this argument?
她已经买了机票了
She already got her ticket.
Ted 这对我来说很重要
Ted,it's important to me.
我就不会邀请Lucy的爸爸
I would never invite Lucy's dad.
我才不管 Tony棒极了
I wouldn't care if\nyou did. Tony's great.
我们也邀请他吧
Let's invite him,too.
不 Tony是我在婚礼上最不想见到的人 明白?
No,Tony is the last person\nI want at our wedding,okay?
Robin是倒数第二个
And Robin is a close second.
Robin很可能已经上飞机了
Robin's probably about\nto get on the plane.
再说她为了来而扔下了很重要的工作
Plus,she left a really\nimportant job for this.
在环境问题和汽油价格居高不下的推动下
Spurred by environmental\nconcerns and high gasoline prices,
混合动力汽车的销售量\n要比上一年提升11%
sales of hybrid vehicles have\nrisen 11% over the previous year.
我该怎么办?
What should I do?
不知道
I don't know.
我也不大赞成邀请旧情人来
I kinda get the no exes thing.
干嘛要一段失败的爱情\n来见证一段成功的爱情?
Why ask a failed romance to come\nand watch your successful one?
这就像邀请西雅图水手队去参加世界大赛
It's like inviting the Seattle\nMariners to a World Series game.
这样会很尴尬的
It's weird for everyone.
什么? 不 Robin必须要来
What? No. Robin has to come.
没错 她是我最好的朋友
Right,she's,like, my best friend.
女性朋友 我最好的女性朋友
Female friend. My best female friend.
我才不在乎 我装什么呢
I don't care,why fake it.
伙计 Robin必须得来
Dude,Robin has to be here.
- 她不该来\n- 你什么意思...
- She shouldn't come.\n-What are you talk...
Aldrin法官 现在1票对1票
Justice Aldrin, tie-breaking vote.
好吧 没有Robin会怪怪的
Okay,wouldn't feel right without Robin.
但是你也不能把新娘给惹毛了
But you don't mess with the bride.
我告诉她不要来
I'm gonna tell her not to come.
- 哦 不 Ted\n- 这是正确的选择 Ted
- Oh,no,Ted.\n- It's the right decision,Ted.
这将会是有史以来最糟糕的通话
This is gonna be,like, the worst\nphone conversation of all time.
Ted Ted Ted 作为你的伴郎 \n我来帮你搞定
Ted,Ted,Ted. Co-best\nman-- I'm on it.
喂?
Hello?
Robin 你在哪?
Robin,where are you?
呃 刚准备去机场
Uh,just heading to the airport.
好的 待会见 一路顺风
Okay,we'll see you soon.\nHave a great flight.
坏消息 电话打不通
Bad news. I couldn't reach her.
Robin已经在来的路上了
Robin's already on her way.
好吧 Robin要来了
Okay,Robin's on her way.
说实在 我很高兴
You know what, I'm glad.
旧情人是可以来参加婚礼的
Exes should be allowed\nto come to weddings.
我只管这样告诉Stella得了\n让她自己去面对
I'll just tell Stella\nshe's got to deal with it.
我觉得你处理这件事要更慎重一些
I think you need to be more delicate\nwith Stella about this whole Robin thing.
你指的慎重是什么意思?
What do you mean by delicate?
在婚礼之前新娘面对的压力很大
Brides are under a lot of\nstress before a wedding.
不过 当然我当时处理得很好
I mean,of course, I held\nit together pretty well.
你忘记了?
You don't remember?
花店老板说那些玫瑰花要比\n中粉红还要浅一些
The florist just told me the roses are\nmore light medium-pink than medium-pink.
浅粉红! 一切都完了
Light medium-pink! Everything's ruined.
我们的婚礼场地用的是重力炉\n而不是用热风采暖设备
Our wedding site uses a gravity\nfurnace instead of forced-air heating.
这是我唯一在乎的了
That's the one thing I cared about.
我们干嘛还要结婚?
Why are we even getting married?
Blobbity-blah.\nWickity-wah.\nBlobbity-blah.\nWickity-wah.
Eeky,eeky,eeky,eeky whee!\nEeky,eeky,eeky,eeky whee!
之后就只听到一阵噪音了
After a while,it's all noise.
可怜的Stella要把一个月的抓狂\n都压缩到这3天里发泄
Poor Stella's had to jam months\nof crazy into just three days.
那我该怎么办?
So what do I do?
你等着下一个危机的到来\n你把它解决掉 你就成英雄了
You wait for the next cris,\nyou solve it,you're a hero.
到时候再提Robin的事 那她就会答应的
Then you bring up the Robin thing,\nbut this time she'll say yes.
对 但是如果没有下一个危机那怎么办?
Yeah,but what if there's no next cris?
她要当新娘了 肯定会有下一个的
She's a bride. There\nwill be a next crisis.
约4分钟后
like four minutes later
另一个危机来了
There's an next cris.
太棒了! 什么危机?
Awesome! What is it?
我的女儿 我的亲生女儿 \n她将不能来参加我的婚礼
My daughter,my own daughter\nisn't coming to our wedding.
什么?
What?
Tony本该明天开车把她带回我这的
Tony's supposed to\ndrive her up tomorrow,
但是现在他对于我要结婚耿耿于怀\n他反悔了
but now he's being all petty about\nme getting married,and he won't do it.
已经都5年了\n为什么我们不能开始新生活?
It's been five years. Why\ncan't we just move on already?
所以 明天我先开车过去\n和他谈谈 让他同意我把Lucy带回来
So first thing tomorrow I drive down,talk\nto him, get him to let me drive Lucy up,
然后 嘣 危机解决了
then,boom,cris solved.
Stella也高兴了 \nRobin也能来参加婚礼了
Stella's happy. Robin\ncomes to the wedding.
- 你就是Barney?\n- 对
- You Barney?\n- Yes.
我听说你就是做"鸭"的\n给我听着
I hear you're a real\nman whore,so listen up.
明晚我想干些既下流又堕落的事
Tomorrow night I want to do\nthings so dirty and so depraved
以至于我都忘了这本来是我的婚礼
that I forget that this was\nsupposed to be my wedding.
我... 我和别人一道来这儿的
I... I'm kind of here with someone.
带她一起来
Bring her.
你绝不会这么做的
You're never going to make it.
结婚那天早上 我去Tony处去接Lucy
The morning of my wedding day I made the\ntrip back to Tony's house to get Lucy.
Tony...\nTony...
在练空手道啊?
Doing a little karate?
抱歉 抱歉 伙计
Sorry,sorry,man.
你触发了我体内的防御警铃
You just set off my\ninternal defense alarm.
你得见识下
You got to watch these things.
- 保持警觉 保持清醒\n- 没错
- Stay alert,stay alive.\n- Right.
什么风把你吹来了?
So what brings you here?
我还以为你早就滚得远远的\n此刻正与我的女人在蜜月套房里呢
I thought you'd be off in some\nhoneymoon suite with my woman right now.
还没 不过快了
Not yet. Soon.
没错 就是今晚了 耶!
That's right, tonight's the night. Yeah!
哦 伙计 你就要和我孩子她妈缠绵了
Oh,man, you are going to be sticking\nit to the mother of my child.
事实上 我已经和她缠绵过很多次了
Actually,I've already stuck\nit to her plenty of times.
为什么每次我都得去纠正别人?
Why do I always have to correct people?
你和Stella
You and Stella.
你们这对幸运的家伙 我本可以...
You lucky dog. I could just...
我真为你们感到高兴
I'm so happy for you guys.
嗯 嗯 喂 听着\n有一个事情 Lucy她...
Yeah,uh,hey,listen, here's\nthe thing-- uh,Lucy...
你不能带她走
You can't take her.
Tony 别这样 瞧 \n这一天对于Lucy来说也很重要
Tony,stop. Look,this is\na big day for Lucy,too.
你最好抛开你的私心\n想一想对她来说什么才是最好的
You're going to have to put aside your own\nissues and think about what's best for her here.
不管你情不情愿 \n她真的应该参加她妈妈的婚礼
Whether you like it or not, she really\nshould be at her mother's wedding.
那么 我带Lucy一道回去啦
So,I'm taking Lucy with me.
伙计 你是对的 你是对的
You're right,man. You're right.
我很抱歉 我很抱歉 \n我只是看见你们俩...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's\njust... seeing you guys...
让我意识到了我曾经拥有的一切
has made me realize everything I had.
咱能别抱了吗
let's stop hugging.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
Lucy就是我的一切
Lucy means the world to me.
我感觉我就要失去她一样\n她所在的新家庭里已经没有我了
And I feel like I'm losing her to this new\nfamily-- a family I'm not even a part of.
哦 别这样 当然有你啊
Oh,come on,sure you are.
不 不是的 \n我都没被邀参加婚礼
No,I'm not. I wasn't even\ninvited to the wedding.
好吧 你现在受邀了
Well,you are now.
公路旅行 对吧?
Road trip. Right?
公路旅行第二回--\n重回车中
Road Trip 2--\nBack in the Car.
那么 就是今天了
So,today's the day.
你准备好了吗?
You hydrating?
亲爱的雌性动物 \n谢谢你对Barney Stinson感兴趣
Dear femal thank you for your\ninterest in Barney Stinson...
我会让你的背变成Jackson Pollack那样\n(美国现代抽象表现艺术画家)
Your back is going to look\nlike a Jackson Pollack.
我很遗憾的告诉你这次...
I regret to inform you\nthat at this time...
我曾当了两年素食主义者
I was a vegan for two years.
我需要尝尝荤的
I need meat.
最近已经没有席位空缺
there are currently\nno positions available.
我是个瑜伽教员
I'm a yoga instructor.
任何姿势都可以
Every position is available.
去你的房间 20分钟以后\n不需前奏
Your room,20 minutes. No foreplay.
我不会这样做的 对不对?
I'm not going to make it,am I?
决不能
Not a chance.
好 记着 让我先跟Stella说\n好吗?
Okay,just rember, let me\ntalk to Stella first,okay?
妈妈! 妈妈!
Mommy! Mommy!
Ted邀请了爸爸过来!
Ted invited Daddy!
嗨 宝贝 我想死你了
Hi,sweetie. I missed you.
等妈妈一会儿 好吗?
Give me just a sec,okay?
嗨 Tony
Hey,Tony.
你邀请了Tony来参加我们的婚礼?
You invited Tony? To our wedding?
Ted我们已经说好了的\n我们的婚礼上不许有前任情人
Ted,we talked about this.\nNo exes at our wedding.
你为什么要这样做?
Why would you do this?
哦 Ted这次又干了些什么?
Oh,boy. What did Ted do this time?
Ted Robin怎么在这?\n我想我的意思你已经很清楚了的
Ted,what is Robin doing here?\nI thought I made myself clear.
我们的婚礼不许出现前任情人
No exes at our wedding.
公平起见... 你前夫也在这呢
To be fair... your ex is here.
是你邀请的他!
You invited him!
拜托 这一点也不别扭
Come on,it's not weird.
太别扭了
It is weird.
感觉好像你们之间还有些什么纠缠
It's like things are not\nfinished between you two.
还有Tony...
And Tony...
我现在无法应对Tony
I can't deal with Tony right now.
你能不能出去 叫他离开?
Can you please go out\nthere and tell him to leave?
你可以说是我要求的
You can make me the bad guy.
我去和Robin谈\n这样她就知道这无关私情了
I'll go talk to Robin,so she\nknows it's nothing personal.
好吧
Okay.
孩子们 \n如果当时我让Stella去找Robin谈
And,kids,if I had just\nlet Stella talk to Robin,
这个故事的结局也许就会不同了
this whole story might\nhave ended differently.
- 我明白\n- 我理解
- I understand.\n- I get it.
第一次\nTed和Stella Mosby
For the first time,\nTed and Stella Mosby.
这就是我和你们老妈的浪漫史
And that's how I met your mother.
吧啦 吧啦 吧啦 \n你们老爸的废话唠叨完了吗?
Blah,blah,blah. Is your\ndad finally done yakking?
去吧 谁想吃冰激凌?
Now,come on, who wants ice cream?
但我没这么做
But I didn't.
你能和Tony谈吗?
Look,can you talk to Tony?
Robin从东京一路飞来
Robin flew all the way here from Tokyo.
我得和她谈谈
I should talk to her.
当然
Sure.
对不起 我就那样跑开了
Sorry about running off like that.
哦 没事了 \n你绝不会相信这是个什么样的旅行
Oh,it's okay. You would not\nbelieve the trip I just had.
我几乎在飞机上待了一天
I was on a plane for almost a full day.
但是来看你结婚 还是很值得的
But it is worth it to\nsee you get married.
- 我怎么能不来呢\n- 你不能参加婚礼了
- How could I not be here...\n- You can't come to the wedding.
- 哦 谢天谢地!\n- 什么?
- Oh,thank God!\n- What?
Ted 这太别扭了
Ted,it's weird.
- 这不别扭\n- 确实别扭
- It's not weird.\n- It is weird.
你知道作为新人的前任情人来\n参加婚礼是什么感觉吗?
Do you know how it feels to be\nsomebody's ex at their wedding?
- Robin.\n- Stella\n- Robin.\n- Stella.
靠 婊子! 我赢了!
suck it, bitch! I win!
我们分手都一年多了
We broke up over a year ago.
对 但是这时间还不够久
Yeah,but that's not that long ago.
看你娶别的女人\n这并不是我期待看到的事
Watching your marry another woman isn't\nexactly something I was looking forward to.
我不明白 我想如果我改变了对\n婚姻和孩子的看法...
I don't know, I just thought if I ever changed\nmy mind about marriage and kids, it was...
如果你还未婚 我会觉得也许我们还有可能
it was nice to know that you were there.
我就是你的避风港--真够奉承的
So,I was your safety\nschool-- how flattering.
不是这样的 只是...
That's not it. It's just that...
你为什么还要提起这些事?
Why are you bringing any of this up?
我们之间已经没什么了
There's nothing between us anymore.
也许有呢
Well,maybe there is.
我的意思是 当然还有
I mean,of course there is.
还有那些不会消失得不留痕迹的事
That kind of stuff doesn't\njust disappear without a trace.
嘿 我并不仅仅是一个客人 Ted
Look,I'm not just\nanother guest here,Ted.
好吧 我们以前约会过 \n但是我们都有新生活了
Right. We used to date,\nbut we both moved on.
瞧 我们都得到了想要的东西\n我要结婚了 \n而你在东京找到梦想的工作
And,look,we got what we wanted-- I'm getting\nmarried, you got your dream job in Tokyo.
- 从此我们就过着幸福的生活...\n- 我辞掉了工作
- And they all lived happily ever...\n- I quit my job.
什么?
You what?
我要搬回纽约
I'm moving back to New York.
我以为我想要那份工作 但是...
I thought I wanted that job, but...
我想要回到现实生活
I want to come back to my real life.
我想你也应该这样
And I think you should go back to yours.
什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
不要结婚
Don't get married.
你看 你太仓促了
Look,you're rushing into this.
就好像是你要提前跳到故事的\n结尾一样
It's like you're trying to skip\nahead to the end of the book.
Ted 你是我见过的最浪漫的人
Ted,you're the most romantic guy I know.
你为我偷过一个蓝色的法国小号
You stole a blue French horn for me.
你试着祈雨
You tried to make it rain.
- 我确实祈到了雨\n- 那是巧合
- I did make it rain.\n- It was a coincidence.
那么多事情之后 \n你就这样终止了对浪漫的追寻?
But after all that, this is how your\ngreat romantic quest comes to an end?
你就消失了 和别人结婚 共组家庭
You're just disappearing into someone\nelse's wedding, someone else's house,
和别人生活\n别无他想
someone else's life\nwithout a second thought.
这不是你渴望的美好结局
That's not the amazing\nending that you deserve.
这不是Ted Mosby的风格
That's not Ted Mosby.
我爱Stella \n她就是我要的那个人
I love Stella. She's the one.
如果你真的这么想...
If you really feel that way...
我想你不参加婚礼还真是件好事
I guess it's a good thing you're\nnot coming to the wedding after all.
大吵一架?
Big fight?
对
Yeah.
拿着...
Here...
- 店里请客\n- 再给我倒几杯
- It's on the house.\n- Just keep 'em coming.
哦 天啊 一杯足矣
Oh,God,do not keep them coming.
嘿 Robin
Hey,Robin.
Barney\nBarney.
今天我糟糕透了
I am having a horrible day.
我从免税店顺了点苏格兰威士忌\n要一起喝吗?
I snuck some scotch in from the\nduty free store. You want to join me?
好 好 \n去你的房里喝 离这远远的
Yeah,yeah. Let's go to your\nroom. Far away from this room.
我们还能一口气喝完
And we can knock it back.
他们没给我准备房间
They didn't get me a room.
我只是想能和你待在一起
I was actually hoping\nI could stay with you.
没问题
No problem.
我还得小小收拾一下
I just have to straighten\nup a little bit.
我有些衣服散落在地板上 还有...
I've got some clothes\non the floor,and...
还有一个绑在你床头板上的裸女
And a naked girl tied to your headboard.
毛巾落在洗手间 确实很乱
Towels all over the\nbathroom. It's a mess.
那么...
So,anyway...
给我十分钟来整理一下房间...
give me ten minutes to\nget the place in order...
再见 Barney
See ya,Barney.
她...
She...
好 我们来干吧
Okay,let's do this.
见鬼 这是谁?
Who the hell is that?
嗯 她是前台小姐
Um,it's the girl from the front desk.
孩子们 \n有时你们觉得你们活在一个故事里
Kids,sometimes you think\nyou're living out one story,
但事实上 故事可能彻头彻尾的改变
but the truth turns out to\nbe something else entirely.
那时 我想这事无非是关于Robin\n是否应该来参加婚礼
At the time I thought the story was about\nwhether Robin should be at the wedding.
实际上我没搞明白真正的故事是什么
If only I'd understood\nwhat the real story was.
前任情人出线在那场合...
Having exes around...
我说不好\n是有些未完待续的事吧
I don't know,it brings\nup unresolved things.
你怎么知道如果前任情人就坐在身边\n你们不会重新擦出火花
How do you know that that spark won't\ncome back with your ex sitting out there?
就好像是你们之间还有纠缠
It's like things are not\nfinished between you two.
我浪费几年时间来让Lucy她爸决定\n他是否已对此最好了准备
I wasted years trying to get Lucy's\ndad to decide if he was ready for this.
看着你们这样...
Seeing you guys...
它让我意识到我曾经拥有的一切
it's made me realize everything I had.
我曾经也梦想过Tony像你这么主动
I used to dream that Tony\nwould be spontaneous like this.
说真的 孩子们 \n绝对不要邀请前任情人来参加你们的婚礼
Seriously,kids,never invite\nan ex to your wedding.